foreign
[Music]
helped me understand why do you want
revenge against Sonic the Hedgehog he
hasn't done anything to you
don't tell me you forgot already dumb
boy Finn and his brother embarrassed us
at a random tournament finally ending
out to your long-winding streak
as the king of games it is our job no
our massive esteeming duty to stand Atop
The Competition
I doubt anyone even remembers that you
lost everyone loses some matches from
time to time it's part of the game but
that's what makes dual monsters so fun
to face strong opponents
how dare you call duel monsters again
it's not a Dame it's a way of life
duel monsters is everything to me
without it what the [__] am I really
besides the ghost of an ancient Egyptian
pharaoh that died long ago when the
pyramids were still up
so you're just embarrassed that you lost
yeah but if I challenge him to a duel he
will just defeat me again so I have new
plans now a way to get rid of him and
remind people that I am the greatest
duelist to ever live
Pharaoh you don't mean what I think you
mean
yes little partner it's time to bring
out the Dual armor
[Music]
I'll be right out Bartle babe I just
have to drop a dookie
hub
what is this put it on Sonic today we
fight and figure out who is the
strongest of them all
yamiyuki somehow I knew that you would
return the face me for Revenge
why can't you just take your loss like a
man instead of ambush people in public
bathrooms because I don't want to now
stop stalling so we can see who the king
of games truly is
I was going to secretly film by [__]
taking a crap but instead he's in
trouble I should do something before
Yuki hurts him luckily I always carry
this dual armor around with me wherever
I go
don't even try it our pal U Keys got a
job to do in there and we promised him a
little privacy you dig you're not seeing
him without going through us first
and then put of your Duke's Japanese
teenagers will settle this old school
by the way Sonic do you know how to
activate your dual armor
actually no can you show me how I
perfect Tristan come in the bathroom and
release my dual capsule
oh
[Applause]
come forth the ultimate wizard in terms
of attack and defense the mighty Dark
Magician
this wielder of magic is ready to suck
on some balls
[Music]
yeah
now it's time to silence that evil voice
he fused with his Dark Magician
yeah I'm going to use the Dual armor to
beat your ass
[Music]
just as I expected
Pegasus what are you doing here
oh me I was on my way to watch the
cartoon Little Bill
ever since Bill Cosby was outed as a
sexual predator it makes Little Bill
just that much more exciting
but first I had to go take a big dumpies
and I am going to wipe my ass with a
very special card
that's my grandpa curse you Pegasus did
you use your Millennia and I to
interrupt my grandfather so again
oh this is going to be such fun
the truth is I never did for your
grandpa impossible my grandpa who sent
home after I defeated you at the Duelist
Kingdom he's home safe and sound
he's telling the true few key
Grandpa
I'm not your grandpa Yuki my real name
is Bobby because it's hired me to trick
you and it worked because I kind of
looked like your real Grandpa your real
Grandpa soul is still trapped in that
card and has been for many years
UK will you ever forgive this foolish
old man
[Music]
I forgive you and I will always love you
you will always be my grandpa to me
no I won't
Pegasus I'll deal with you later right
now I have more important [__] to do
first
how do I use the Dual armor
you won't
dark magic attack
Yuki what are you doing Sonic hasn't
even transformed yet at least give him a
chance to defend himself
silence the king of games does whatever
the [__] he wants and I command both of
you to activate your dual armor and
stand at my side so we can destroy the
blue to learn
activate dual armor red eyes [__]
dragon
activate dual armor key mace
take a look at the Sonic it seems like
you lost our little game but you were
never good at games were you I knew it
you must have cheated during out last
Duo how else would you be doing so bad
this time for shame I wanted to have
some more fun but I suppose I expected
too much from a fat person
dark magic attack activate dual armor
Elemental Hero flame wingman
it's the real Elemental Hero flame
wingman wait no bro is that you
sup bro you didn't think I would let my
bro fight all on his own did you
hurry up and use that dual armor so we
can wipe the floor with these bastards
but I don't have my Yukio cards with me
they got you covered big blue
try this card on for size
it matches your big bubble butt
activate dual armor
Elemental Hero Bubble Man
Joey used the powers of your red ass
bigger dragon and stop him don't let him
transform but if he transforms it will
be a fair fight
some exactly dumb picks
Bubble Blaster
ghost kind Dives culture attack
Joey is unconscious as [__] he [__]
lost don't you think I can't see that
noob if he was better he could have
thought that bubble but he didn't so now
it's your turn to fight go before they
send you to the shadow realm again
I'm starting to think you never had a
plan in the first place
Bubble Blaster
UK help me
fart Tristan fart out of your pet if you
fart the bubble will expand and it will
pop floating the room with you
disgusting guests
[Music]
I can't Yuki it's no use that's all the
juice I've got in the tank
don't stop you income dupe
if you fart the bubble will explain and
it will pop
[Applause]
damn it let me out of here pop this
bubble and release the king of games at
once it is way into stinky
not this time pero I'm afraid it's time
to earn your Just Desserts now which of
you let's want to come give this one
tour a hand
thank you foreign
[Music]
B I will have my revenge against you
someday oopsies I think Daddy has to
poop is
[Music]